Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
No.
What is not?
Let's go. I will tell you on the way.
Let's go. I will tell you everything.
Welcome.
10,000,000 won.
Fine. You are just a man worth just that much.
Come out. I will tell you everything.
Episode 9
She's not at the cooperative there either.
Is that so? She has always been in the lab and she didn't even leave a note, where did she go?
She's also not picking up her phone, right?
Yeah. She's not answering.
Okay. Go to the house and keep searching.
Gi Hoon went home to look.
A blue curtain
This room which doesn't even have a single bright lipstick.
This is a room of a 26-year-old woman.
How could it be...
that there isn't even a little stuffed animal in here.
That bad girl who I thought didn't know how to smile.
Where did she go?
Somewhere, is that bad girl smiling again?
Song Eun Jo is Han Jeong Woo's woman forever.
Oppa, you were here.
What is this?
Song Eun Jo is Han Jeong Woo's woman forever.
Han Jeong Woo? Is that your roomate?
Song Eun Jo...
So he knew Eun Jo
ever since she was Song Eun Jo.
♫ Again today my memory led me astray ♫
♫ I who am strolling at the end of the street ♫
♫ Where you can't hold me again ♫
♫  I ask again about the way ♫
♫ Saying that I want to see you ♫
♫  and hold you again ♫
♫ While looking at heaven I am praying ♫
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I cannot be without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
♫  I don't mind if my heart breaks ♫
♫ because, yes, you are the only one I love ♫
Will you hold on to me?
If you hold on to me, I think I will be able to stop now.
Before I board the train,
hold on to me, Eun Joo.
The bad girl that I love.
I knew you were very tough.
But I didn't know you would easily ignore my earnest plea for you to hold on to me.
I really didn't know.
It's all over. Believe me.
Right? It's done.
You said you would die. You threatened me that you would die.
I didn't want you to die so I ended it.
I am not fooling you for a while but it's for real.
So until now,
all this while, you two met?
Yes.
What are you saying? We didn't meet for three years in between.
Won't you shut it?
So if you don't meet now
if it's the end as you said
then you could meet after some time again.
You won't believe me even if I say I won't.
How could I? Would you believe it if you were me?
You lie whenever you open your mouth, then cover it up with another lie.
What the truth is, can you even differentiate it?
Do you even have sincerity?
Shut up and listen to me, wench.
You thought you were able to fool everyone without being caught, you thought no one knew, right?
You thought it was easy to make a naive man a fool?
I... got rid of that man.
I gave him money so that he will get off me.
If I gave money to get him off it means I made a resolve already.
What is this? What does this mean?
I will get off. I will not take this money and get off.
No matter how bad I am, I know how to be ashamed.
To you, I already showed you everything.
I have nothing to show.
This brat who followed to see me die. Bad wench.
Are you relieved?
I could have gotten this though.
How could you make this everyday? It's tiring.
It's not tiring. Hurry and drink it.
I don't like you, Honey, coming to work everyday.
It would be best to leave it to someone, and for now
stay at home taking easy walks at times while resting.
I'm going. If you can't go home for dinner tonight,
call me. I'll bring you something.
Go with Hyo Seon's father.
A problem came up at the factory. Take him home.
Think of any excuse. No matter what, he can't be here.
Don't let him pick up any calls either. Hyo Seon's father can't undergo any shock anymore.
Why? What's wrong?
Take him with you and go on a trip for a few days.
That'll be better. Please, Mom.
Please tell me why you suddenly can't supply us with rice anymore.
No, but if you suddenly—
Hello? Hello?
What did they say? Why can't they supply rice for us?
Wait... Can't we purchase rice from somewhere else?
Didn't you read the contract?
It says we can only use organic rice from the Gyeonggi-do area.
How can you do this? How can you suddenly do this?
This is not the first deal you've done with our Dae Seong True Wine Makers.
How can you just suddenly break your promise overnight?
This is a breach of contract!
Breach of contract? What breach? Did we even sign a contract?
What did you say?
If we signed a contract, then there should be a physical contract. Bring it over.
We have been supplying rice to you all this time,
but that's not a contract. We provided the rice first,
and President Goo Dae Seong would pay us with revenue from rice wine sales later.
We've been supplying the rice without a contract all this time and you're not even thankful.
Young people these days...
Then who's getting the rice originally meant for us?
I don't know. I'm off work now, so let's leave it at that.
Managing Director...
- Excuse me, Ajusshi!
- Wait, Ajusshi.
You don't remember me?
I haven't been here for a while now,
but I came here with my dad to play when I was young.
You don't remember?
I'm Hyo Seon! You said I was pretty and even bought me candy.
You even fed me rice wine as a joke before!
Oh! That daughter.
Yes! I'm that daughter.
Ajusshi, don't leave
and just have one cup of rice wine with us. Please?
Thank you, Ajusshi. We won't take much of your time.
Cheers!
Ajusshi, have one more cup.
I shouldn't drink any more.
- Pour me one too.
- All right.
Why is a kid like you so good at drinking?
Please accept one more cup!
Ajusshi, who bought the rice
that was meant for us?
Why don't we meet that person tomorrow instead?
We don't have time.
It's night time.
We're going now. The days are flying by.
Even if we get the rice tomorrow, we may not even be able to make the deadline.
Are you going to argue with him this late at night just like you did with the director just now?
In adults' eyes, they will only consider that disrespectful.
Oppa, did I do well today?
I did well, didn't I?
Yes, you did well, Hyo Seon.
As long as Oppa is watching, I can do everything well.
I'll go with Hyo Seon tomorrow.
I'll do it.
You don't trust Hyo Seon?
She's more capable than you are.
You can't find your way to others' hearts.
Is that so?
You won't get any answers with the way you act.
You're a pro at having people lock their hearts up.
Stop the car.
Stop the car?
There's just one thing I want to ask you.
Back then ... when I left,
why didn't you come to the train station?
You didn't get my letter?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I told Hyo Seon to give you a letter
asking you to come to the train station.
Did Hyo Seon, perhaps, not give it to you?
I got it.
You did?
You got it...?
I don't even remember if I ripped it up or burned it after reading it.
Is that something I have to remember?
You didn't come even after reading it?
Stop acting like a beggar.
- What did you say?
- What are you begging for?
You want to relive the past with me? There's nothing I can give you.
Stop asking me about the past! I told you there's nothing!
♫ Even if there are wounds left in my heart now ♫
♫ I am told to forget about you ♫
♫ But even if I bite my lips and bear it ♫
You didn't get my letter?
♫ You are the only one who is my person ♫
♫ I am living day after day ♫
♫ In your name  ♫
♫ when tears appear again, woo  ♫
♫ I can't bear it  ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again. ♫
Hyo Seon didn't give it to you?
As long as Oppa is watching,
I can do everything well.
One...two...
Honey, look here.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Drink it before it cools.
What is it? You want to make a call?
I'm wondering how the factory is doing.
Just forget about the factory while we're here. The children can handle it.
Let's go over there. There's a nice place over there.
- I'll take it.
- It's okay. Let's go.
Go faster! Faster, faster!
Run! Run!
Faster! Faster!
Giddy-up! Run fast!
We can't export.
What do you mean?
The person who bought all the rice says they'll sell it to us for three times the cost.
What did you say?
If we pay three times the cost for the rice we need to make the rice wine, it'll cost more to make than the profit for selling it.
I'm going to tell Dad right now.
No. Don't say anything to him.
How can we not tell him about it?
Just come home without saying anything to him! Hang up.
Wow, so strong!
Now, strong! Wow! So fun!
You're not going to answer me even if I ask what's wrong.
Right. I won't answer. You're being bothersome. Go outside.
Okay. But drink first. I'll leave after I see you drink it.
I'll drink it, so leave.
I'll leave after I see it.
That honey tea is good for mental and physical stability. And it's good for your upper digestive...
I said to go outside.
If you tell me to die, I could die.
You have to eat in front of me the things I tell you to eat.
Oh, man. What's so hard about drinking that?
Are you sleeping well?
Where are you going?
Yes, I understand. I'll leave now, so you guys go on to the factory. Okay.
Is there something wrong, Honey?
You've lost all color in your face. Are you okay?
I'm okay. Let's get going now.
I said I'm okay. If you treat me like a patient, I'll get upset at you.
I'm not treating you like a patient. It's because I like holding onto you.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Please let me see the documents.
This is the export contract. Do you think a loan will be possible?
We'll let you know the results of the review by tomorrow morning at the latest.
Do you need money?
Use my money.
My entire life's savings that I gave you. Use it.
Didn't I tell you? I said I'll be responsible for your life.
Hey. Does that even make sense? You're going to purchase it at three times the original cost?
What would be left over after that?
What's the difference between doing that and just ending our business now?
Daeseong's reputation already hit rock bottom because of our last incident.
If we can't fulfill our orders this time, it'll be nearly impossible to rebuild our name.
So what? You went to the bank as you pleased with a contract?
You want to take out a loan? What happens if we can't pay it back?!
What will happen if we can't repay the loan?!
Why can't we repay it? If we successfully get this order through, we can get back on our feet again.
How do you know that will happen?!
I know, so why don't you know?
How is it possible that you don't know it?
What did you say?
The "Dae Seong" of "Dae Seong Cham Do Ga", is your father's name.
Even before you were born, people drank rice wine associated with your father's name.
This time if it's known that Dae Seong Cham Do Ga failed to fulfill its promise to fill in this order,
your father's name will be ruined.
Can you allow that to happen? Your own father's name?
Stop acting like you're thinking of my father!
You think you care more than I do?
More than me?
Goo Eun Jo cares more than Goo Hyo Seon?
Don't be hypocritical!
Don't say that it's to protect my dad's name.
It's better for you be honest and say it's so you'll have more to take later.
Isn't that it?
It's not?
If it isn't, say it isn't true.
Why can't you say it?
I said, say it!
How can you know what's in my heart so well when I don't even know.
What?
What are you so afraid of that you keep asking me to reveal my inner thoughts?
Who said I was afraid?
How much I'll take away... is that what you're afraid of?
No. Or is it that you're afraid of me becoming a more important person than you?
If that's not it either, then are you afraid that I'll take everything away and leave nothing for you?
- Do you think I'll let you take it?
- Let's just assume I had other intentions.
Even if I did, I wouldn't tell you. This is immature and unbearable!
The reason I'm this patient with you is because you are your father's daughter.
Where do you think you're going? Say that again.
Let go.
What? Immature and unbearable?
Immature and unbearable!
You're so unbelievably immature
I'm going crazy just imagining the unbearable consequences of your actions!
What? The results of my immaturity?
What do you mean?
That's enough. It's all in the past and I don't want to talk about it.
I asked you what you meant.
Do you really want to know?
If you don't tell me, I'll kill you.
Will you really not regret it?
Stop playing around and tell me.
That person's letter...
Why did you keep it and not give it to me?
You, making me say this,
and even standing with you is unbearable. But I'll let it go.
Not for you but because you are your father's daughter.
Goo Hyo Seon.
Not giving you the letter...
you're calling that immature, right?
Then ...
the unbearable results of my immaturity...
What's that?
You want to fall into the gutter with me?
Must you really listen to me say it?
Tell me ...
before I kill you.
For me
since I was born into this world...
for the first time ...
for the first time...
Since nothing will change, I won't make an issue out of it anymore.
I don't want to be the main character in a story of two stepsisters fighting over one man.
I’ve stepped out of that story a long, long time ago. I'm not going back to it.
So, you keep your mouth shut.
But there's something you need to be careful about.
That man...
doesn't seem to have gotten over me yet.
Isn't that funny?
Dae Seong Cham Do Ga is passing over a bump right now.
Since they have deep roots, I believe they will be able to stand right up once they pass this bump.
As you've seen, even until just 5 years ago,
they've grown well without a single loan from the bank.
There's not even a speck of dust in their operations.
Right. So, what are your plans?
Their eldest daughter is called Eun Jo.
She's working on developing a scientific yeast.
She spends all day and night studying yeast to unify the taste of the rice wine.
She's smart and a talented woman so it's only a matter of time before she succeeds.
It's possible that the yeast that woman develops will become the core of Dae Seong Cham Do Ga.
We must have that as well.
I need you to find out who's behind the rice prank.
I suspect it's the joint effort of smaller businesses,
but we need solid information to be sure.
One more thing.
Eun Jo found out it would be hard for her to find a loan from the bank for the amount she needs,
and is searching for funds from third-parties.
That little one is so determined...
I cannot allow Dae Seong to get funds from third parties. You should help them.
It will be ours anyway.
E-so Savings Bank
This has the best conditions of all the ones I've looked into.
I think we'll get the amount we need.
Is that really true?
It's true.
If you've looked over everything, please stamp here.
Loan Application
Hey! You worked hard!
You guys all worked hard,
You went through a lot, Dad..
I'm going to the lab. I haven't been there for a long time.
Eun Jo.
Let's have lunch together.
I don't want to.
Unni.
Let's eat together, okay?
Let go.
I'm my dad's daughter.
You said you'll let it go since I'm my dad's daughter. Where are you going?
If you leave now,
I have to watch my dad's heart hurt over not having fed you.
You can't go.
Eat and go, you evil bitch.
I feel so good.
Whatever the results be, because you all helped me,
I feel like I was able to blow my nose without using my hands.
Dad, why are you talking about blowing your nose while we're eating?
It's so delicious.
Eun Jo, will you pour me a drink?
Would you like one?
- No.
- There you go again, being so cold.
All right then, I'll drink Eun Jo's alcohol.
- Gi Hoon, pour me a drink.
- Yes.
Stop drinking, you have to stop drinking,
Do you want a drink?
Yes. Thank you, Unni.
You take one.
Here.
You two...
Oppa Gi Hoon, leave with Dad first.
I want to have a drink with Unni today.
That's enough. Eun Jo can't drink.
No, I can. Let's have a drink together, Hyo Seon.
Drink...
You...
Can you leave our family?
Leave.
Get out.
Why?
Because I feel like I'm going to kill you soon.
I really hate you.
Yet you once said you really liked me.
I never said that.
You never said that?
You used to annoyingly follow me around.
Leave.
My officetel in Seoul is still as is.
Someone like you can get a job anywhere.
You'll have no problem surviving.
If you have difficulties, I'll even give you my allowance.
Leave.
Please leave.
Seeing your face at home, at the company and at the factory
every day is insufferable.
I feel the same way.
Yeah. It's insufferable for you too.
So leave.
No.
Did you think I'd agree?
You think I'd agree really easily?
Didn't you say let's give this a try?
Didn't you want to compete and see who will win?
You're the one who said all that.
Why?
Does it seem like you'll obviously lose,
so you don't want to fight anymore all of a sudden?
If you keep being like this,
I'll really take everything away from you.
You think I can't do it?
Dae Seong True Wine Makers, your father...
and even the person you like...
I'll take them all from you.
That's what you've been really thinking since the start...
Song Eun Jo.
It's Goo Eun Jo.
I'm Goo Eun Jo.
Whether my last name is Song or Goo doesn't really matter but,
if you keep acting like this...
Should I?
Should I really take it all from you?
Should I see how much I can really take from you?
Can I do that?
You're so wicked.
♫  Leaving behind the time ♫
♫  which was buried in my heart ♫
♫  I said I longed for you ♫
♫  and waited for you ♫
♫  Even my memory which turned away ♫
♫  doesn't know that I longed for you ♫
♫  Looking only in this direction ♫
♫  my two eyes ♫
♫  can't say they waited for you ♫
♫  I can't say I'm coming back ♫
♫  Will you who knows everthing about me ♫
♫  who cannot forget you ♫
- Hey.
♫  return to me? ♫
♫  If there are tens of thousand who will just love you ♫
♫  If I can always look at you ♫
♫  The day I return to your side again ♫
♫  will come again ♫
Find these girls.
Where on earth are they? What are they doing that they won't answer their phones or come home?
I called the place where they were drinking during the day, and they said they left a long time ago.
- We'll go look for them.
- These girls...
Honey, you have a phone call. It's a Japanese person.
A Japanese person?
Hello. Yes.
What does this mean?
The ship arrived in Japan, but
he said that the receiver of our container didn't show up.
This... what is this supposed to mean?
I'll contact the company in Japan and find out immediately.
Hey, Gi Hoon. He said no such company exists.
Pardon?
Honey, honey!!
I'm okay... I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
It was a dummy company. All the documents were fake.
Did you do this, Father? Was it you?
It was Gi Jeong.
Who?
I just found it out now. It was Gi Jeong's doing.
Hong Gi Hoon is on the line. Shall I put him through?
- Put him through.
- I understand.
It's me.
Were you the one who did it?
I don't know a bit of what you're saying,
Did you want Dae Seong Cham Do Ga that much?
Were you always this sneaky, Hyung Gi Jeong?
I never imagined this from the eldest son of Hong Joo Ga Corporation.
I didn't see you as someone who would take down someone's company
using an thug's underhanded trick like this.
Was this really the action of Hong Gi Jeong, the eldest son of Hong Joo Ga corporation?
Is this your family's doing?
You've been in contact with your Hyung Gi Jeong?
Ahjussi.
Who's arguing to whom about being underhanded?
I actually took a blow from you.
I heard you used Father's money to buy that rice back. Congratulations.
For now, Dae Seong Cham Do Ga is going to be in yours and Father's hands.
But don't let your guard down. I only did this as a test.
If you take business so lightly, do you think you can last long?
How could you...
Ajusshi.
How could you do this to me?
He passed away before you arrived.
Be quiet.
How dare you talk when you don't know anything?
Honey. Joon Soo's dad...
Honey.
Dad...
Mom.
What happened to Dad?
Hyo Seon, wake your dad. Don't let him sleep.
Dad.
Hyo Seon is here.
Where should I start first?
No matter what, I want to do it all for you.
You can rely on me.
For the time being, I'll be the reason for you to stay here.
I like him. So what? I like him. I like him because there's a lot I can take from him! Why?
Don't abandon me.
If you don't, I'll be grateful.
Can you call me Dad just once?
Dad, no!
Dad! You can't! You can't. Dad.
How can this happen?
Stop it. Be quiet.
Dad! Wake up!
Be quiet, Hyo Seon. Stop it!
Dad. Dad.
What are you saying? Honey.
- Dad, look at me.
- Get up right now, honey!
Dad.
I did this.
I stole these two pretty girls' father away from them overnight.
I swear...I didn't mean for this to happen.
Can you call me Dad just once?
You won't call me Dad?
All right. I know you don't want to.
- D...
- Dad!
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I cannot be without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ because, yes, you are the only one I love ♫
♫ My bruised heart is shouting so ♫
♫ I can find you ♫
♫ Wherever you are ♫
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫